Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Electric – Nursery School Panel Circuits, 1928 (Box 40)
- Electric – Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #4 From Main Line at Horse Barn to Rombout [Bill], 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #4 ffrom Main Line, Raymond Ave., To Pole Rear of Mr. Arthur’s House [Bill], 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Location of Electric Manhole, uncovered Jan. 24, 1933 (Box 40)
- [Electric – Main Building Street Lights], 1931 (Box 40)
- Electric – Service to Professor Treadwell’s House, Nov. 1931 (Box 40)
- Electric – Sketches for Proposed One Line Diagram Map of Electric Service, Feb. 19, 1931 (Box 40)
- Electric – Taylor Hall Lighting Service Repairs Work Order #325, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Distances Between Manhole Centers Taken Mar. 4, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Street Lamps 1928 Construction (Box 40)
- Electric – Service to Mr. Arthur’s House Measurements Taken February 13, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Beginning of Electric Service to Farm – Measurements Taken Feb. 13, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Electric Service to Taylor Hall, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Dimmer Layout at Vassar College, 1932 (Box 40)
- Electric – 1929 Electrical Construction to Mr. Arthur’s House from Main Line on Raymond Ave. (Box 40)
- Electric – New Electric Bypass Around Steam Manhole North of Chapel, 1933 (Box 40)
- Electric – Service to Kenyon Hall Sketch Showing Location of Starting Point (Stake) of Survey, 1933 (Box 40)
- Electric – Angle for Electric Ducts to Nursery School, 1927 (Box 40)
- Electric – New Electric Service to Warden’s House, 1933 (Box 40)
- Electric – Manholes 1-4, 1939 (Box 40)
- Telecommunications – [Telephone Lines, Vassar College], 1939 (Box 40)
- Electric – Replacement of #6 Weatherproof Wire with #2 from Main Line at Horse Barn to Cow Barn [Bill], 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – Replacing Cable Between Steam Manholes No. 7 and 8, Raymond Ave. June 16, 1948 (Box 40)
- Electric – Proposed New Duct, Manholes and Cable from Steam Manhole Just East of Chapel to Alumnae House, 1945 (Box 40)
- Electric – Skinner Hall and Physics Lab Street Lamps, 1931 (Box 40)
- [Building Surveys – 1928-1949] (Box 40)
- Sewer – Skinner Hall, 1931 (Box 40)
- Sewer – Wing Farm, 1969 (Box 40)
- Sewer – Sewer Line Check, January 1950 (Box 40)
- Sewer – President’s House, 1938 (Box 40)
- Sewer – Sewer for Vivarium, 1944 (Box 40)
- Sewer – Playhouse, North of Kenyon Hall, 1938 (Box 40)
- Work Order 817 – 2” H.P. Line to South Side Academic Buildings, 1934 Construction (Box 40)
- Grounds – College Avenue Area, 1927 (Box 40)
- Grounds – Walks and Roads West of Main Building, 1932 (Box 40)
- Grounds – Section South of Vassar Lake and South East Avenue and Raymond Avenue and Denney’s Property, 1938-1967 (Box 40)
- Heat – Avery Hall- Details for Reconstruction of Heating System. 1934 (Box 40)
- Grounds – Skinner Hall Area, 1931 (Box 40)
- Van Ingen Hall – Standing Radiation, 1937 (Box 40)
- Kenyon Hall Heating Survey, 1944 (Box 40)
- Ely Hall Radiation, July 29, 1942 (Box 40)
- Greenhouse Radiation, 1932 (Box 40)
- Total Number of Square Feet Radiation in Buildings Heated By Vassar College [Voided October 20, 1932] (Box 40)
- Josselyn Heat (Box 40)
- Heat To Skinner (Box 40)
- New Heating Duct to President’s House, 1931 Construction Estimate (Box 40)
- Blodgett Hall – Proposed A.C. March 2, 1951 (Box 40)
- Electric – Measurements Taken After Duct Construction, Taylor Hall, 1936 (Box 40)
- Location of Electric Manhole East of Chemistry Lab, 1927 (Box 40)
- Electric Manhole Drawings, 1927-1944 (Box 40)
- Details of Heating Tunnel at Physics Lab, April 1928 (Box 40)
- Heating Branch to Greenhouse, 1930 (Box 40)
- Manhole Plan (Box 40)
- Library Heating Indirect, 1937 (Box 40)
- Heating Service Estimates, 1926 (Box 40)
- Location of Hot Wells in Relation to Boiler House (Box 40)
- Heating Reports for Skinner Hall and Greenhouse – May 7, 1930 (Box 40)
- Heat to Gym, May 9, 1930 (Box 40)
- Heating Reports – 1926-1934 (Box 40)
- [Square Foot Radiation Survey, Oct. 19, 1932] (Box 40)
- Sewer From Good Fellowship Clubhouse, 1937 (Box 40)
- Heat – Kenyon Hall, 1933 (Box 40)
- Electric – Street Lights Sketches, 1927-1947 (Box 40)
- Heat – Heating Duct to Vassar Brothers Lab and New England Building, 1934 Construction (Box 40)
- Heat – Services and Piping Raymond and College Avenue Houses, 1926-1928 (Box 40)
- Electric and Telephone – Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 40)
- Electric and Telephone – College Avenue Houses, 1944 (Box 40)
- A.C. to Blodgett, Nov. 1938, also quotations on M.G. Set (Box 40)
- Electric – Replacing Electrical Service to Alumnae House from Manhole North West of Williams Hall, 1941 Construction Work Order 412 – A (Box 40)
- Electric – Kenyon Hall, 1933-1949 (Box 40)
- A.C. to Kenyon Hall from Manchester Road Summer 1949 (Box 40)
- Estimate-Proposed Street Lamps, Gray Wing Farm, 1937 (Box 40)
- Equipment Journal for Easley (Blodgett) Library (Box 40)
- Equipment – Coal Larrie and Chute, Boiler House, 1946 (Box 40)
- Equipment – Metal and Woodworking Machinery Survey, April 1941 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Lectern from Room 35 Rockefeller (Box 41)
- Equipment – Coal Conveyor and Crane, 1927-1930 (Box 41)
- General – Services to the Dean’s House, 1931 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Stoker Drive (Steam) and Motor, 1927 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Boiler Feed Pump, 1927 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Euthenics (Box 41)
- Equipment – Vassar College Track Dimensions (Box 41)
- Equipment – Stoker Speeds and Gearing Boilers 1,2 and 5, 1927-1933 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Flat Ironer, 1932 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Preliminary Sketches for Blodgett Hall Vertical Sliding Blackboard Auditorium (Box 41)
- Equipment – Ventilating Fan, Taylor Hall, Basement Sept. 23, 1936 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Moulton Journal Case, Chemistry Lab Library, April 22, 1935 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Motor (Box 41)
- Equipment – Sketches of Nose and Throat Treatment Equipment as is installed at Dr. Krieger’s Office, 1934 (Box 41)
- Equipment – Goulds Pump-B.B. Layout, 1933 (Box 41)
- Water – Water Mains, 1934 Reconstruction, Raymond Ave. and College Ave. and Campus. Work Order 813 (Box 41)
- Electric – Street Lights Estimates etc., 1931-1938 (Box 41)
- Water – Farm Greenhouse Rombout Skinner, 1927-1947 (Box 41)
- [Water – Water Line Construction, 1927] (Box 41)
- [Water – 6” Universal Pipe and Hydrant] (Box 41)
- Water – 300,000 Gallon Storage Tank Piping and New Fire Pump, 1937 Construction (Box 41)
- Water – College Avenue Section, 1927 (Box 41)
- Water – 6” Water Service to Baldwin, 1939 Construction (Box 41)
- Water – Golf Course, Water Tank, Tabard, Hockey Fields, 1930-1949 (Box 41)
- Water – Kenyon Hall Area, Water Piping, 1927, 1931, 1933, 1935, 1949 (Box 41)
- Water – Blodgett, Cushing, Nursery School, 1938 (Box 41)
- Water – Kendrick House, 1926 (Box 41)
- Water – Nursery School and Wing Farm Area – Water Piping, 1933-1938 (Box 41)
- Water – Chemistry, Physics, Avery Open Air Theatre, 1933 (Box 41)
- Water – South Campus, 1926, 1929, 1935-1936, 1941, 1944, 1950, 1955 (Box 41)
- Water – College Avenue, 6” Water Main, Ferrell House-Welch House (Box 41)
- Water – West Section of Campus, 1926, 1946-1947 (Box 41)
- Water – Water Meter List, January 21, 1932 (Box 41)
- Water – [Proposed Water Main Connection Between Main Building and Boiler House to Service Buildings], 1947 (Box 41)
- [Water – Coal Bunker], 1936, 1950 (Box 41)
- Water – North Hall Cold Water Piping Layout in Building, 1941 (Box 41)
- Water – Location of New Hydrants, August 15, 1927 (Box 41)
- Water – Laundry Water Consumption, 1940 (Box 41)
- Water – 1926 Construction Universal Pipe and Fittings Laid, Work Order 43 (Box 41)
- Water – Water Meters to be Installed, 1928 (Box 41)
- Water – Position of Fire Plugs in Front of Proposed House, 1926 (Box 41)
- Old Gas Holder East of Infirmary Change Order, 1937 (Box 41)
- Water – Location of Hydrant in Rear of Avery Hall, 1926 (Box 41)
- Water – Water Meters Near Pump House (Box 41)
- Water Lines or Fire Lines (Box 41)
- Water – Water Lines and Consumption Reports, 1927-1931, 1946 (Box 41)
- Gamon Meter Company Water Meter Quote, 1928 (Box 41)
- Water – Town of Poughkeepsie Water System Notes, 1943 (Box 41)
- Water – Water Meter Installation and Survey, 1928 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Wing Farm Surveys, 1930 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Vassar Lake Survey, Fall of 1942 and other Information (Box 41)
- Grounds – Skinner Hall, 1941 (Box 41)
- Fulton Ave. Property – John Ogden (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Ely Hall, 1926. 1928-1929, 1944,1948 (Box 41)
- [Sewers and Drains] – Baldwin House, 1939 (Box 41)
- [Sewers and Drains] – College Avenue Sewer, North Side, Work Order 628-A, May 5, 1944, 1945 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Raymond, Davison, Strong, Lathrop, Jewett, Josselyn, 1926, 1938, 1949 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Cushing House and Vicinity to 1932, 1927-1932 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – New Garage (East of Boiler House), Boiler House, Pump House, Sewer Pump House, P.P. Superintendent’s House, 1927, 1930, 1938, 1950 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Palmer House, 1938, 1945 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Raymond Avenue Sewer and Tie to Campus and Locations of Some Faculty Houses, 1926, 1931,1942 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Library, 1949-1950 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Main Building, 1927,1938 (Box 41)
- Sewers and Drains – Blodgett and Nursery School, 1928-1949 (Box 41)
- Sewers – Kenyon Hall, 1933-1935 (Box 41)
- Drains – Kenyon Hall and Cemetery Drains, 1927, 1933, 1944 (Box 41)
- Rough Estimate – Sewer From Pierce House, 156 College Ave. to Manhole North of #160, 1945 (Box 41)
- Sunset Lake, South End Dam Bridge, 1952 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Alumnae House Road and Walk, 1931 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Raymond and College Avenue Surveys, Survey around Dean’s House, 1931 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Alumnae House Road, 1931, 1943 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Chapel, 1927, 1935, 1940, 1949-1950, 1954 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Alumnae House, 1951 (Box 41)
- Buildings – General, 1938-1942 (Box 41)
- Library – Van Ingen, 1939 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Blodgett Hall, 1941-1949 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Booth House, 149 College Avenue, 1945 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Coal Pockets, Cottage Street, 1943-1945 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – 145 College Avenue, 1948 (Box 41)
- Eleanor Conservatory (Outside Dimensions) January 4, 1933 (Box 41)
- Co- op. Housing Unit – Property Services etc., 1949 (Box 41)
- Cushing House, 1951-1952 (Box 41)
- Buildings – ‘D’ Cottage, 1942-1944 (Box 41)
- Doctor’s Garage – Measured February 2, 1942 (Box 41)
- Vassar College (Main Building), (Student Living Area Only) (Box 41)
- Ellis House, July 23, 1940 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Davison, 1949-1957 (Box 41)
- Flagler House – Attic, 1946 (Box 41)
- Gow House, 141 College Avenue, 1947-1948 (Box 41)
- Greenhouses, 1927-1941 (Box 41)
- Hill House – For Fire Escape, 1946 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Jewett Hall (North), 1942-1957 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Ely- Avla Set-ups (Sketches), 1941-1943 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Ely Hall General, 1933-1944 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Ely Hall Geology, 1934-1936 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Farm, Cow Barn, East Poultry House, 1932 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] Fire Pump House – Building Sketches, 1937 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Garage – East of Boiler House Sketches of the Existing Old Coal Bunkers etc. (Box 41)
- Buildings – Josselyn House, 1948 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Kenyon Hall, 1941 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Hughes Farm House – Sketches of Floor Plans, 1940-1942 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Ice House Later Garage (Garage Destroyed by Fire Night of Nov. 24, 1929) (Box 41)
- Buildings – Kendrick House, 1948 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Low Cost Housing Project – Vlackte Area (Faculty Projects), 1941 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Main Building Estimates etc., 1947-1950 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Lyman House, 147 College Ave. 2nd Floor Proposed Apartment, 1943-1950 (Box 41)
- [Buildings – Main Building Floor Plan Sketches], 1926-1937 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Metcalf, Proposed Addition to the Kitchen, 1939 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Nursery School (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – New England Building, Proposed Additions to the Present Balcony, 1955 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Palmer House, 1931-1939 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Palmer Apartments (proposed), April 1939, 1939-1954 (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – Detail Warden’s House (Pratt) (Box 41)
- [Buildings] – President’s House, 1935-1946 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Power House Sketches of Power House and Coal Bunkers – used in connection with Unit No. 5, 1932 Construction, 1931-1935 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Raymond and College Avenue Houses (House Sizes), 1932 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Raymond Baths Etc., 1941-1954 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Riley House – Jan. 25, 1954 [Floor Plans] (Box 41)
- Buildings – Sewer Pump House [Dimensions], 1942 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Sheet Iron Storage Building (For Furniture), Proposed, 1935 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Skinner Hall, 1929-1932 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Students Building, 1939-1960 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Tonks House, 1954 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Van Ingen, 1948 – 1950 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Williams House, 1948 – 1951 (Box 41)
- Buildings – Paul E. Zehe Estate, 100 Overlook Road, New Rochelle, N.Y. Sketches of Floor Layout and Inventory of Furnishings, Taken Jan. 11-12, 1944 (Box 41)
- Gas – [Gas Lines to Davison and Prof. Fite and Washborn Houses], 1927 (Box 41)
- Gas – Gas Service to Nursery School and Cushing Hall, 1946 (Box 41)
- Gas – Location of Central Hudson Gas and Electric, 1932-1943 (Box 41)
- [Gas – Plans and Surveys], 1938-1943 (Box 41)
- Outdoor Theatre Stage – May, 1961 (Box 41)
- [Gas] – Gas System-1939 and 1940 Construction, 1940-1943 (Box 41)
- Ecological Garden Survey for Skinner Hall Site, Nov. 1929, Also Along Easterly Side of Raymond Ave. (Box 41)
- Josselyn House – Rear Wing – West Side, 1954 (Box 41)
- [Grounds – Transit Stations and Flagstone Walks], 1939-1946 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Baldwin House Area, 1939 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Blodgett, Cushing, Kenyon, Nursery School Area, 1926-1938 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Chapel Gate, 1931 (Box 41)
- [Grounds] – College Ave. Property, 1948 (Box 41)
- [Grounds] – Flower Circle and Surrounding Area Showing Location of Trees and Walks, 1952 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Original Land Purchases By M. Vassar [Transcribed] (Box 41)
- Grounds – Wing Farm Surveys, 1939 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Hockey Fields and Tennis Courts, 1927-1932 (Box 41)
- Dr. McCracken – Hornyback, Oct. 1942, 1926 (Box 41)
- Lisburne Grange, 1946-1947 (Box 41)
- Quadrangle Elevations – May 28, 1951 (Box 41)
- [Vassar College Farm Road and Pond Measurements], 1959 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Ice Hockey Rink Northeast of Kenyon, 1936 (Box 41)
- Grounds – Skinner Hall Bridge, 1944-1946 (Box 41)
- Grounds – New Concrete Sidewalk West of Main Building, 1941 Construction, 1941-1945 (Box 41)
- Heating and Electrical Ducts, 1931-1949 (Box 41)
- Heat – Baldwin House (New Infirmary), 1939 (Box 41)
- Studio Arts – Cost Estimates and Budgets, 1991-1993 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Bidding Summary and Backup, 1992 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Construction Contract and Misc., 1992 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Construction Contracts, Owner/Contractor, 1992 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Constituents Fees, 1993 (Box 42)
- [Studio Arts Center] – Expenses, 1994 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Supplemental Instruction, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Requests for Information, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts Center – Schedules, 1993 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Field Reports, 1992 (Box 42)
- [Studio Arts] - Technical Reports, 1993 (Box 42)
- [Studio Arts Center] – Soils Testing Report, 1992 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – Change Order Requests and Estimates, 1993 (Box 42)
- Studio Arts – FF and E Invoicing, 1993 (Box 42)
- Seely Mudd, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
- Pull Sheet Wiring Code (Box 42)
- College Center Specifications [1973] (Box 42)
- Mudd Chemistry Building Specifications, 1982; (2 folders) (Box 42)
- Budgets / Estimates / Value Engineering, 1996 (Box 42)
- Correspondence File, 1994 (Box 42)
- Blodgett [Construction] Estimates, 1994-1996 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall Renovation] – Schedule, 1996 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall Renovation] – Pre Design Phase (Box 43)
- Blodgett – Anthropology NSF [National Science Foundation] Grant (Box 43)
- Blodgett – Master plan, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
- Anthropology NSF [National Science Foundation Grant] Phase I Design, 1993-1996 (Box 43)
- Blodgett NSF [National Science Foundation Grant 1994, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] - Program, 1993 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – General, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] - C.III. Architect Selection Phase, 1990-1994 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – RFP, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – A/E Proposals, 1994 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – A/E Contract, 1993 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – C.IV – Design Phase, 1994 (Box 43)
- Draft Schematic Design Report, 1994 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Anthropology Project, 1997 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Ancillary Space Needs, 1996-1997 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall Correspondence and Acoustic Testing], 1996 (Box 43)
- Blodgett Moves 1998 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Schedule, 1997 (Box 43)
- Blodgett – Construction Document Estimates, 1997 (Box 43)
- [Blodgett Hall] - Status Reports File, 1996 (Box 44)
- Blodgett – Front End Documents, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Cannon Contract Invoices and Change Orders], 1997-1998 (Box 44)
- Cannon Contract / Claims etc., 1998 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Cannon Fees, 1994-1999 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Cannon Re-imbursements, 1995-1997 (Box 44)
- Signed Contract / Purchase Orders, 1996; (7 folders) (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] - Financial File, 1995-1996 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] - Contractor Qualifications, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Addenda, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Approved Change Orders, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Pending / Proposed Change Orders, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Bid Meetings, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Bids Received, 1997 (Box 44)
- Storm King, 1997 (Box 44)
- U.W. Marx – Blodgett, 1997 (Box 44)
- Kirchoff, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Bid Evaluations, 1997 (Box 44)
- Blodgett – Re-bid, 1997 (Box 44)
- GC MC and EC Bids / Schedule of Values, 1997 (Box 44)
- [Blodgett Hall] – C.V. Bidding Phase, 1997 (Box 44)
- Blodgett Auditorium, 1998-1999 (Box 44)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W/P Project Budget and Budget Status Reports, 1998 (Box 44)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W/P Project Studies / Surveys, 1992 (Box 44)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W / P Project Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 45)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W / P Project – Hoffman Architects, 1998 (Box 45)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W / P Project – Kirchoff, 1998 (Box 45)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W / P Project – Storm King, Proposal/P.O. / Invoices, 1998 (Box 45)
- Blodgett A / V, 1997-1999; (2 folders) (Box 45)
- Blodgett Hall – Ext. W / P Project Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] - Submittals and Shop Drawing File, 1998 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] –Requests for Information, 1998 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – General, 1997-1998 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – FFandE, 1997 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Telecommunications (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Hazardous Materials, 1997 (Box 45)
- Project Monitors Report for Vassar College – Blodgett Hall Renovation Abatement Project ,Omega, 1997 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Environmental, 1997 (Box 45)
- [Biofit], 1997 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Geotechnical, 1996 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Site Survey, 1996 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Permits, 1998 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Future Work at Blodgett Hall, 1996-1998 (Box 45)
- [Blodgett Hall] – General Correspondence, 1996-2000; (2 folders) (Box 45)
- Blodgett – Correspondence, July – December 1999 (Box 45)
- Blodgett – Boiler Feed and Condensate Return, 1999 (Box 46)
- Open CPR’s, 1998 (Box 46)
- [Change Orders 1 -19], 1997-1998; (19 folders) (Box 46)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Correspondence, July 1998 – June 1999, 1998-1999; (4 folders) (Box 46)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Correspondence, 1997, January – June 1998, 1997-1998; (3 folders) (Box 47)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Meeting Minutes, January 1999 (Box 47)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Job Meetings – 1 Jan 1998 to 31 Mar 1998 (Box 47)
- [Blodgett Hall] – Job Meetings – 1997, 7 Apr 1998 – December 1998, (3 folders) (Box 47)
- [Cannon Invoices (Blodgett Hall Renovation / Phase 2), 1996-1997; (3 folders) (Box 47)
- DASNY [Dormitory Authority of the State of New York] - I / D Requirements (Box 47)
- DASNY [Dormitory Authority of the State of New York] – Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 47)
- DASNY [Dormitory Authority of the State of New York] – Change Orders 1 – 15, 1998; (2 folders) (Box 47)
- DASNY [Dormitory Authority of the State of New York] – Change Orders 16-20, 1998 (Box 48)
- Forms (Box 48)
- Moving Issues / History, 1997 (Box 48)
- Religion Move, 1997 (Box 48)
- Weekly Schedules, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
- Construction Alerts / Notices, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
- Roof Inspection Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 48)
- Soil Testing, 1998 (Box 48)
- Concrete Testing, 1997 (Box 48)
- Hydraulic Elevator Inspection, 1998 (Box 48)
- Acoustical Testing, 1998 (Box 48)
- Field Reports By Cannon, 1997 (Box 48)
- Magnetic Door Locks Issue, 1998 (Box 48)
- Storm King Contract, 1997 (Box 48)
- [U.W. Marx Construction Bid], 1997 (Box 48)
- General Contractor Reference Check (Box 48)
- [Adelaide Environmental Health Associates Inc. Proposal], 1997 (Box 48)
- Darlind Construction Inc. Bid Proposal [Blodgett Hall], 1997 (Box 48)
- Andron Construction Bid Refusal, 1997 (Box 48)
- Accu-Labs Inc. Analysis [Blodgett Hall], 1995 (Box 48)
- Blodgett Hall invitation To Bid, 1997 (Box 48)
- Blodgett Financial, 1998-1999 (Box 48)
- Banner Reports, 1998 (Box 48)
- IV. B.2 Permits – Town of Poughkeepsie, 1998 (Box 48)
- IV.B.7 – Site Boring – Tectonic Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 48)
- IV.A.10 – Site Survey – Chazen, 1996 (Box 48)
- IV. B. 8 – Reimbursables – Various, 1997 (Box 48)
- IV. A.7 – Cost Estimator – Daedalus Projects, 1996 (Box 48)
- IV.A.3. Architect Fees (DD,CD,CA) – Cannon, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
- II. C – Hazardous Materials – Asbestos Crop / Omega Environmental, 1997 (Box 48)
- II –B-6- Telecommunications, 1998 (Box 48)
- II.B.2 – Electric/Transformers – Rondoubt, 1997 (Box 48)
- III – Furniture, Fixtures, Equipment, 1998 (Box 48)
- IV.B.9 – Miscellaneous Expenses – Various, 1998 (Box 48)
- IV.B.5 – Moving/Relocation – Various, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
- IV.B.6 – Material Testing – Soil and Material Testing, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
- IV. B.10 – Physical Plant – BandG (Service Orders), 1998-1999 (Box 48)
- Miscellanious Purchase Orders, 1998 (Box 48)
- I.A.1 – General Construction – Kirchoff Construction, 1997-1999 (Box 49)
- Correspondence VC [Vassar College] / RAM, 1998 (Box 49)
- [Blodgett Hall Electrical Bids], 1997 (Box 49)
- [Plumbing Bids, Blodgett Hall], 1997 (Box 49)
- [Mechanical Bids, Blodgett Hall], 1997 (Box 49)
- Closed [Requests For Information], 1997-1998 (Box 49)
- Open [Requests For Information], 1998 (Box 49)
- Bi-Weekly Staff Meetings, 1998 (Box 49)
- Air / Water Balancing, 1998 (Box 49)
- Transmittals, 1997 (Box 49)
- [Blodgett Hall Renovation Floor Plans (Cannon Bid Set) 1997] (Box 49)
- Vassar College Blodgett Hall Renovations Operations and Maintenance Manual (Vol. I) (Box 49)
- Vassar College Blodgett Hall Renovations Operations and Maintenance Manual (Vol. II) (Box 49)
- Closeout Manual Division 2-6 (Box 49)
- [Closeout Manual (Division 7-16)], 1997; (4 folders) (Box 50)
- [Construction Information (Blodgett Hall Renovation)], 1997 (Box 50)
- [Kirchoff Construction Correspondence, Blodgett Hall Renovation], 1998 (Box 50)
- [Blodgett Hall Renovation Submittals (Electric, Telecommunications and Fire Alarm System)], 1998 (Box 50)
- [Blodgett Hall Renovation], 1998; (3 folders) (Box 50)
- [Blodgett III], 1996 (Box 50)